Round 7 of the Championship Finals.
Get ready, go!
Show me rock, John Ken Poe!
And the winner is Killua!
Yes!
Very nice, and now here's your prize, the Sword of Truth.
Whoa, hey, check it out, Goan.
Card number 83, it goes in a specified slot.
Alright, one card down, score!
天使の微笑みで連れ出して
孤独でも一人じゃないさ
生まれてきたことに必ず意味がある
You can fly again!
太陽浴びて
You can fly away!
世界は君の輝きを待ってる
大地を踏みしめて
君は目覚めてゆく
天使の微笑みで連れ出して
始まりはいつでも大さくないさ
何度でも立ち上がれ
大地を守る
The problem is, how are we gonna protect the card?
Well, we don't have any defensive spell cards, so we should probably get some.
Wait! Yeah, you kids!
Hand over the Sword of Truth right now!
Look, I don't want to have to rough you up, so just do what I tell you!
No way, you idiot.
Hold on! Fuck!
Fuck!
You're bluffing, right?
I already know that you just started playing the game a little while ago.
You're both newbies, so you haven't obtained any defensive spells yet except for the Sword of Truth.
This is Thief!
This spell card lets you steal one random card from another player's specified slots.
Take this! Thief on! Attack Kilo-
Haven't you trained at all, mister? Nice try.
I won't give it back the next time.
You must be an amateur. This is a game for pro hunters. I'm impressed that you even made it in.
But at least we learned something. An attack spell won't kick in until you finish the chant.
Yeah, but a strategy like that only works on the very weakest players!
Exactly.
If you want a card, you just take it from someone else. Only fools actually participate in tournaments.
Understand, boys? If not, you will.
They really pissed me off!
Just forget it. Those guys are all pros. At least they didn't use brute force.
Damn it! Then I've really gotta start focusing hard on building up my spell cards!
In that case, I say we should head out to Masadora, the City of Magic.
Sounds like a plan!
That's our hideout!
We're gonna start off by assigning roles. Everyone here right now will be collecting spell cards for us.
You've probably heard there are 40 different spell cards. We need you to obtain one. Fortress.
This is one of the strongest defense spells in existence, and we could certainly use another one of those.
It will help us to protect Angel's Breath.
What the hell is Angel's Breath?
It's a super rare card with an SS rank that no one has ever been able to get their hands on.
How can you be sure no one's ever obtained it?
There's a spell card called List.
Casting it tells you the current conversion number of one card, as well as the number of people who have it.
Yeah, okay.
The card is incredibly difficult to obtain, because you need to have all 40 spell cards in your possession before you can trade for one.
Of course, spell cards are extremely useful in this game, so players tend to use them up.
But now, after a whole lot of searching, we've completed our collection of all 40 spell cards.
What we'd like to do is trade them in for an Angel's Breath card right now, but...
If you did, you'd have nothing to protect it with. That's why you need a copy of the Fortress, correct?
Exactly. That said, in order for this plan to work, what we want you to do is to make a complete list of the 40 spell cards and commit them to memory.
Those four Gargayder cards got us 120,000.
I know, they were pretty valuable. We don't need to worry about money now.
Hey, why don't we buy some food and water? Then we'll head to Masadora.
Sure, but first we need a map.
The one with information costs 650,000, and the blank one's only 20.
Which do you want?
The blank one! That way, we get all the fun of filling it in ourselves!
You're so positive it's painful.
Game!
Wow, this doesn't tell us anything.
Let's ask for directions.
Head north for 80 kilometers. After you pass by the mountain, you'll get to a lake.
You're gonna want to follow that lake north for a little while, and it'll take you right to Masadora.
If we hurry, we can do, like, 80 kilometers a day.
Assuming that you survive, of course.
Huh?
That mountain is practically crawling with bandits. Even worse, after you pass the mountain, you'll encounter hordes of monsters.
There's bandits? And monsters?
Now it's starting to sound like an RPG.
Let's see what the monsters look like!
Come on, hurry!
Alright, move out!
Wait, please!
I'm begging you.
For what?
I'd really like to join you if you don't mind.
No way. Sorry.
But may I ask why not?
You'd slow us down.
How dare you speak to me that way, you little brat!
I could take you out with one hand tied behind my back if I wanted to!
That does it.
I was only planning to mess with them for a little while, but now I'm going to completely ruin their lives!
Hey! Hold it right there!
I mean, please! I'll try really hard not to get in your way! I promise!
Okay, I have most of the information we need.
Then, can you tell us what you've found?
Of course. I'll start with number one.
I tried a hundred different people in this city, and they all gave the same response when faced with an unusual question.
That's typical behavior for non-playable characters.
Number two.
Book.
This copy is real, and this one's a copy Kortipi made.
Gain.
Kortipi's didn't transform.
I believe that might indicate that the game's program didn't recognize Kortipi's card.
And three.
Shizuku's vacuum seems to function normally in this world, but it won't work on any items that have special abilities of any kind.
I think that's because the game was programmed to prevent Nen abilities from being used to collect cards.
I see.
So?
However, these three points indicate yet another possibility.
This game isn't taking place in a virtual world. It's based somewhere in the real world.
But what do you mean?
You see, if any of the players were to actually enter Greed Island, then their souls would fully detach from their bodies and enter the console, leaving their bodies behind.
Sending them in physically wouldn't be necessary.
And while separating body and soul might be possible, it would take a lot more than standing in front of a console and using Hatsu.
It would make a lot more sense if the players were actually teleported somewhere else entirely.
Therefore, the software operating the console has nothing to do with playing the game.
Its job is to teleport players who trigger it with Hatsu to this island.
That stands to reason, but I don't think I get what it means.
The big reward for clearing the game. You remember it?
Let's see. What was it?
Of all the cards you've found for your specified slots, you can choose three and take them all back to the real world with you.
That's right. And that means that every one of these items are available to be used outside of the island.
If this game does indeed take place in the real world, then it should be possible to remove all of the treasure without actually having to clear the game.
Understood.
Book.
So at the moment, we only know a little bit about a few select items. It would be most beneficial to learn about all the cards.
To start, we need the spell card called Eye of God.
And then we just need to find Finks and Phaeton.
Another cheap map, huh?
Still, he was carrying a lot of spell cards.
Well, wanna split up for now? Let's meet back in Masadoria in a week.
We'll see which one of us can kill more players. Make it a race.
Okay, but be sure to take their cards first.
So what do you think we should do about her?
Just ignore her. We'll have a chance to ditch her once the bandits show up.
But isn't that kinda mean?
What are you talking about? She passed, right?
So she's got strong Nen abilities. She can escape if it gets rough.
She's keeping up better than I thought she would.
Their stamina isn't half bad. Well, for a couple of brats anyway.
You ready?
Mm-hmm.
Please help us. We beg you.
The disease is spreading.
It starts with a mild fever, but then it gets progressively worse and worse until the afflicted finally dies.
All we can do is use medicine to keep the fever at bay.
Sadly, the medicine only works for about a week.
It's also incredibly expensive. And now, we're completely out of money.
We're all sick, so we can't even steal what we need like we normally would.
Could we catch it? It's probably just part of the gameplay.
Help us! My son only has two or three more days to live!
Would you be so kind as to give us some money? Every little bit helps.
So this is part of the game too, right?
Yeah. If we just give them the right amount of money, then they'll probably reward us with some good items or some information.
So, uh, how much do you guys need?
80,000 Jenny.
But that's all the money we have.
Yeah, it sounds like they know everything about us, doesn't it?
Excuse me, but I have enough to cover the 80,000 Jenny.
Excuse me? We're busy, so shut up for a minute.
I'm gonna kill that brat!
Okay, we got it. We'll give you the 80,000 Jenny.
You really will?
Thank you both so much! You've just saved my poor son's life!
I... I'm so cold! So very cold!
This is awful! If his body gets even a little bit colder, he's going to die before we can get the medicine into him!
If only we had some children's clothes for him! Why don't we have clothes?
I guess I could give him what I'm wearing.
Can you really? You're just like angels sent to us from Heaven. Mere words aren't nearly sufficient to express the depth of our gratitude!
Oh, no need to thank us.
Unless you've got items or info.
Hm?
We got nothing!
We gave all of our clothes away and now we're totally broke, too!
Dammit! They're messing with us!
I wonder what that was all about.
But as soon as we get past this mountain, we'll find lots of monsters, right?
Yeah! If we beat a few of them and turn them into cards, we can sell them for cash!
And then we might finally get to start fighting!
Time to see what you've got!
You've got!
You too!
I want to see what you've accomplished in your secret training!
I can't wait!
This area's really rocky.
Let's go for it!
Yeah!
I can't wait!
Whoa! There are tons of them!
Whoa!
Ugh!
Gone's attack didn't do anything?
I guess punches aren't gonna do it.
And there are so many.
To disable one with a single attack?
Bingo! We go for the eye!
Book!
Gone! Just came for the eye!
I got it!
They're moving around way too much,
but otherwise not bad.
They were weaker than they looked.
Yeah, but after we left it alone for a minute,
the card reverted.
We can do this easy, Gone.
Every one of these monsters comes with a built-in weakness.
Just gotta stay calm and think.
Alright!
Now let's head for Masadora!
Yeah!
Oh!
Gold!
Uff!
I'm okay. See? It didn't even hurt.
This one's pretty weak.
Yeah, but it's really fast. Let's hurry up and catch it!
Damn it!
Aim where it's going to be.
If you watch closely, you can learn an opponent's pattern of motion.
Your eyes are sharp, but you aren't using them properly!
It got away from us.
You know, if the rest of the monsters are this weak,
we're going to get to Masadora in no time.
Ugh, don't be so stupid.
What if you encounter one that's strong and fast?
Are those bubbles?
Huh?
It's gone.
It's loud, and it generates a shockwave.
But there's no real damage.
The red ones don't pop when you touch them.
Actually, the white bubbles pop when they make contact with a human's aura.
The red ones pop when they make contact with anything else.
To catch that horse, you must identify which bubble is which,
and then switch smoothly between Zetsu and Ten.
Unfortunately, that's still too difficult for them.
Still, these boys are... they're...
They're just...
wasting their potential!
They're rough gemstones that will shine with just a little polishing.
But at this rate, they'll run into stronger players or monsters and it'll be...
Game over!
Now this one looks a lot tougher.
That's it!
I've had enough!
Gyo!
Huh?
Keep your eyes on it!
Use Gyo!
You know how, Doja!
Gyo!
See?
The armor's just a puppet!
Attacks aren't going to work against it!
Here it is!
Look, I got the card!
So you guys can use Gyo!
Then why didn't you use it before, huh?
Uh, well, I...
Yeah...
You forgot, didn't you?
Don't just stand there!
Gyo!
Tell me what you see.
The number one.
Very good.
Now listen up.
When I raise my finger, I want you to use Gyo.
Then yell out whatever it is you see, alright?
The same applies if you send anything suspicious.
Use Gyo!
Got it?
And what makes you think you can order us around?
I see the number five!
Correct!
You!
Give me 200 push-ups!
Huh?
It's your punishment!
Get to it!
Hey, what the hell?
Why should I?
Got a problem?
Yeah, you bet I do!
Just who do you think you are, huh?
I forgot.
I should introduce myself.
See, I'm a pro hunter.
The name's Biscuit Kruger.
And 40 years ago, I learned Nen,
and now I'm going to use my knowledge and experience
to give you some much-needed coaching.
You should both be eternally grateful.
You learned Nen 40 years ago?!
You're just a hag!
As luck would have it, the young girl following Gon and Killua
is actually a veteran professional hunter.
Woo!
Subject!
It's not!
It's history to get us out of how early this taking place is so diverse!
You're fields and created simply some light from the taste
you have visible.
It is taking this world alive and you run from and you're in.
You can read it easily as it takes place, but every other reality,
You will be a redCare.
you
me
Coming up, the Great Island Tutorial!